Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations: an inventory
Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1914-06-06/1914-07-11; phaedra2174 (Box 255)
  1914phae.proj.2174C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1914-06-22/1914-07-02; phaedra2175 (Box 255)
  1914phae.proj.2175C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1914-07-03/1914-07-22; phaedra2176 (Box 255)
  1914phae.proj.2176C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1914-07-23/1914-09-17; phaedra2177 (Box 255)
  1914phae.proj.2177C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1914-07-25/1914-10-17; phaedra2178 (Box 256)
  1914phae.proj.2178C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1914-07-30/1915-10-11; phaedra2179 (Box 256)
  1914phae.proj.2179C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1914-09-14/1914-09-28; phaedra2180 (Box 256)
  1914phae.proj.2180C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1914-09-28/1914-11-09; phaedra2181 (Box 256)
  1914phae.proj.2181C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1914-10-09/1917-04-26; phaedra2182 (Box 256)
  1914phae.proj.2182C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1914-11-09/1914-11-19; phaedra2183 (Box 256)
  1914phae.proj.2183C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1914-12-01/1917-03-22; phaedra2184 (Box 256)
  1914phae.proj.2184C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1914-12-08/1916-02-08; phaedra2185 (Box 256)
  1914phae.proj.2185C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1914-12-11/1916-10-31; phaedra2186 (Box 256)
  1914phae.proj.2186C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1914-12-18/1915-01-27; phaedra2187 (Box 256)
  1914phae.proj.2187C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-01-15/1915-01-28; phaedra2188 (Box 256)
  1915phae.proj.2188C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-01-28/1915-02-23; phaedra2189 (Box 256)
  1915phae.proj.2189C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-02-05/1915-02-26; phaedra2190 (Box 256)
  1915phae.proj.2190C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-02-19/1915-03-02; phaedra2191 (Box 256)
  1915phae.proj.2191C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-03-13/1915-03-24; phaedra2192 (Box 256)
  1915phae.proj.2192C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-03-24/1915-04-05; phaedra2193 (Box 256)
  1915phae.proj.2193C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-04-05/1915-04-14; phaedra2194 (Box 256)
  1915phae.proj.2194C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-04-15/1915-04-27; phaedra2195 (Box 256)
  1915phae.proj.2195C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-04-27/1915-05-07; phaedra2196 (Box 256)
  1915phae.proj.2196C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-05-07/1915-05-18; phaedra2197 (Box 257)
  1915phae.proj.2197C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-05-18/1915-05-26; phaedra2198 (Box 257)
  1915phae.proj.2198C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-05-26/1915-06-18; phaedra2199 (Box 257)
  1915phae.proj.2199C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-06-05/1915-06-16; phaedra2200 (Box 257)
  1915phae.proj.2200C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-06-16/1915-06-25; phaedra2201 (Box 257)
  1915phae.proj.2201C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-06-25/1915-07-27; phaedra2202 (Box 257)
  1915phae.proj.2202C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-07-13/1915-09-07; phaedra2203 (Box 257)
  1915phae.proj.2203C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-07-22/1915-07-30; phaedra2204 (Box 257)
  1915phae.proj.2204C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-07-30/1915-08-30; phaedra2205 (Box 257)
  1915phae.proj.2205C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-08-31/1916-01-17; phaedra2206 (Box 257)
  1915phae.proj.2206C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-09-08/1915-09-16; phaedra2207 (Box 257)
  1915phae.proj.2207C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-09-17/1916-01-17; phaedra2208 (Box 257)
  1915phae.proj.2208C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-09-25/1916-01-12; phaedra2209 (Box 257)
  1915phae.proj.2209C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1915-10-12/1916-01-03; phaedra2210 (Box 257)
  128
  1915phae.proj.2210C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1916-01-04/1918-10-30; phaedra2211 (Box 257)
  1916phae.proj.2211C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1916-02-10/1916-04-10; phaedra2212 (Box 257)
  1916phae.proj.2212C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1916-03-17/1916-11-25; phaedra2213 (Box 257)
  1916phae.proj.2213C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1916-04-10/1916-07-10; phaedra2214 (Box 257)
  1916phae.proj.2214C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1916-05-19/1916-10-26; phaedra2215 (Box 257)
  1916phae.proj.2215C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1916-07-20/1921-06-23; phaedra2216 (Box 258)
  M.A.H., A.M.C., L.D.W., G.R.B.
  1916phae.proj.2216C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1916-10-11/1917-03-16; phaedra2217 (Box 258)
  G.R.B., M.A.H., A.M.C.
  1916phae.proj.2217C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1914-04-14/1917-05-05; phaedra2218 (Box 258)
  1914phae.proj.2218C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1917-05-05/1917-07-05; phaedra2219 (Box 258)
  M.A.H., A.M.C., G.R.B.
  1917phae.proj.2219C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1917-07-05/1918-07-19; phaedra2220 (Box 258)
  1917phae.proj.2220C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1918-07-08/1919-11-05; phaedra2221 (Box 258)
  1918phae.proj.2221C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1919-04-25/1920-07-27; phaedra2222 (Box 258)
  1919phae.proj.2222C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1919-09-29/1923-02-09; phaedra2223 (Box 258)
  1919phae.proj.2223C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1920-01-06/1925-04-07; phaedra2224 (Box 258)
  1920phae.proj.2224C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1920-11-15/1921-06-18; phaedra2225 (Box 258)
  1920phae.proj.2225C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1921-04-27/1923-07-18; phaedra2226 (Box 258)
  1921phae.proj.2226C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1921-09-20/1923-06-16; phaedra2227 (Box 258)
  1921phae.proj.2227C
- Observations in Arequipa, 1922-04-18/1923-12-06; phaedra2228 (Box 258)
  1922phae.proj.2228C
  Item is missing from pages 1-45 - there are cut out spaces for those pages.
  Many pages included as inserts / tip-ins at front and back
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1910-11-19/1926-04-06; phaedra2229 (Box 258)
  1910phae.proj.2229C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, phaedra2230 (Box 258)
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1923-07-12/1925-04-02; phaedra2231 (Box 258)
  1923phae.proj.2231C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1923-07-06/1924-07-01; phaedra2232 (Box 258)
  1923phae.proj.2232C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1924-04-19/1925-03-23; phaedra2233 (Box 258)
  1924phae.proj.2233C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1924-05-20/1926-03-27; phaedra2234 (Box 258)
  1924phae.proj.2234C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, phaedra2235 (Box 259)
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1925-04-07/1925-11-18; phaedra2236 (Box 259)
  1925phae.proj.2236C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1925-04-09/1926-09-25; phaedra2237 (Box 259)
  1925phae.proj.2237C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1925-05-02/1926-06-15; phaedra2238 (Box 259)
  1925phae.proj.2238C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1925-05-07/1926-10-21; phaedra2239 (Box 259)
  1925phae.proj.2239C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1926-04-08/1926-11-10; phaedra2240 (Box 259)
  1926phae.proj.2240C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1926-05-19/1926-11-01; phaedra2241 (Box 259)
  1926phae.proj.2241C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1926-10-08/1927-02-11; phaedra2242 (Box 259)
  Annie Jump Cannon, Henrietta H. Swope, Carol G. Folx
  1926phae.proj.2242C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1926-12-14/1927-06-09; phaedra2243 (Box 259)
  Annie Jump Cannon, Henrietta H. Swope, Geraldine E. Clark
  1926phae.proj.2243C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1927-01-17/1937-11-26; phaedra2244 (Box 259)
  1927phae.proj.2244C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1927-02-05/1927-06-01; phaedra2245 (Box 259)
  Annie Jump Cannon, Carol G. Folx
  1927phae.proj.2245C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1927-02-24/1927-06-10; phaedra2246 (Box 259)
  1927phae.proj.2246C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1927-06-10/1927-08-25; phaedra2247 (Box 259)
  1927phae.proj.2247C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1927-07-25/1929-07-02; phaedra2248 (Box 259)
  1927phae.proj.2248C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1927-08-30/1929-07-12; phaedra2249 (Box 259)
  Annie Jump Cannon, Florence Cushman
  1927phae.proj.2249C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1927-10-11/1927-11-29; phaedra2250 (Box 259)
  1927phae.proj.2250C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1927-11-30/1928-05-23; phaedra2251 (Box 260)
  Annie Jump Cannon, Florence M. Campbell
  1927phae.proj.2251C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1928-05-23/1929-06-11; phaedra2252 (Box 260)
  1928phae.proj.2252C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1928-06-08/1929-07-11; phaedra2253 (Box 260)
  1928phae.proj.2253C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1928-11-21/1929-01-12; phaedra2254 (Box 260)
  1928phae.proj.2254C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1929-01-12/1929-08-17; phaedra2255 (Box 260)
  1929phae.proj.2255C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1929-01-31/1929-03-04; phaedra2256 (Box 260)
  1929phae.proj.2256C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1929-03-04/1929-07-18; phaedra2257 (Box 260)
  1929phae.proj.2257C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1929-03-26/1929-04-24; phaedra2258 (Box 260)
  Annie Jump Cannon, Florence M. Campbell, Muriel E. Mussells
  1929phae.proj.2258C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1929-04-30/1929-05-15; phaedra2259 (Box 260)
  1929phae.proj.2259C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1929-05-16/1938-12-13; phaedra2260 (Box 260)
  1929phae.proj.2260C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1929-10-04/1929-11-06; phaedra2261 (Box 260)
  1929phae.proj.2261C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1929-11-07/1930-10-27; phaedra2262 (Box 260)
  1929phae.proj.2262C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1929-11-23/1930-02-19; phaedra2263 (Box 260)
  1929phae.proj.2263C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1930-02-20/1930-03-27; phaedra2264 (Box 260)
  1930phae.proj.2264C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1930-03-20/1930-04-16; phaedra2265 (Box 260)
  1930phae.proj.2265C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1930-04-17/1931-05-19; phaedra2266 (Box 260)
  1930phae.proj.2266C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1930-11-06/1930-12-03; phaedra2267 (Box 260)
  1930phae.proj.2267C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1930-12-04/1930-12-31; phaedra2268 (Box 260)
  1930phae.proj.2268C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1931-01-02/1931-01-31; phaedra2269 (Box 260)
  1931phae.proj.2269C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1931-02-24/1938-03-01; phaedra2270 (Box 261)
  1931phae.proj.2270C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1931-03-10/1931-06-05; phaedra2271 (Box 261)
  1931phae.proj.2271C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1931-04-17/1939-02-23; phaedra2272 (Box 261)
  1931phae.proj.2272C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1931-11-04/1932-11-14; phaedra2273 (Box 261)
  1931phae.proj.2273C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1932-11-15/1937-11-24; phaedra2274 (Box 261)
  1932phae.proj.2274C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1933-01-20/1934-01-09; phaedra2275 (Box 261)
  1933phae.proj.2275C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1918-08-22/1934-01-29; phaedra2276 (Box 261)
  1918phae.proj.2276C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1934-06-08/1935-02-15; phaedra2277 (Box 261)
  1934phae.proj.2277C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1935-02-18/1936-03-31; phaedra2278 (Box 261)
  1935phae.proj.2278C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1936-03-31/1940-05-15; phaedra2279 (Box 261)
  1936phae.proj.2279C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1935-12/1939-03-09; phaedra2280 (Box 261)
  1935phae.proj.2280C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1936-06-03/1936-06-08; phaedra2281 (Box 261)
  1936phae.proj.2281C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1937; phaedra2282 (Box 261)
  No observation/photographic dates are listed
  1937phae.proj.2282C
- Annie Cannon Notebooks, 1939-03-14/1940-06-02; phaedra2283 (Box 261)
  1939phae.proj.2283C
- Visual observations (Peru), 1894-08-01/1896-07-01; phaedra2284 (Box 262)
- Variable Stars in omega Cen, 1898-11-01/1898-12-01; phaedra2285 (Box 262)
- Variable Stars in omega Cen, M5, 1899-02-01/1901-08-01; phaedra2286 (Box 262)
- Variable Stars in M3, 1900-06-01/1901-09-01; phaedra2287 (Box 262)
- [Variable Stars] M3, M5, 1901-12-01/1912-09-01; phaedra2288 (Box 262)
- [Variable Stars] NGC 7078, 6656, M22, 1901-07-01/1920-10-01; phaedra2289 (Box 262)
  Solon Irving Bailey, Benjamin A. Gould
- Miscellaneous Variables and NCG 7078, 6656, M3, M5, 1902-01-01/1915-12-01; phaedra2290 (Box 262)
- Variable stars in many clusters, 1922-05-01/1923-02-01; phaedra2291 (Box 262)
- Star Counts, Neb. on Map of Sky, LMC, Glob., 1906-03-01/1907-01-01; phaedra2292 (Box 262)
- Nebulae, 1907-01-01/1908-09-01; phaedra2293 (Box 262)
- Nebulae, 1908-09-01/1911-10-01; phaedra2294 (Box 262)
- Positions of Nebulae, vol. 1, 1908-04-01/1908-07-01; phaedra2295 (Box 262)
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 3, 1908-09-01/1908-10-01; phaedra2296 (Box 262)
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 4, 1908-10-01/1908-12-01; phaedra2297 (Box 262)
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 5, 1908-12-01/1909-03-01; phaedra2298 (Box 262)
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 6, 1909-02-01/1909-04-01; phaedra2299 (Box 262)
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 7, 1909-04-01/1909-08-01; phaedra2300 (Box 262)
  G9
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 8, 1909-06-01/1909-09-01; phaedra2301 (Box 262)
  G10
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 9, 1909-09-01/1909-10-01; phaedra2302 (Box 262)
  G11
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 10, 1909-11-01/1910-08-01; phaedra2303 (Box 263)
  G12
- [Positions of Nebulae], vol. 11, 1910-08-01/1910-09-01; phaedra2304 (Box 263)
  G13
- [Positions of Nebulae] marked by Dr. Shalley, 1., 1923-07-01; phaedra2305 (Box 263)
  G14
- [Positions of Nebulae] marked by Dr. Shalley, 2., 1923-07-01/1923-08-01; phaedra2306 (Box 263)
  G15
- [Positions of Nebulae] discovered by D. Menzel, 1., 1922-07-01/1922-08-01; phaedra2307 (Box 263)
  G16
  Donald Menzel
- [Positions of Nebulae] discovered by D. Menzel, 2., 1922-08-01; phaedra2308 (Box 263)
  G17
- [Positions of Nebulae] discovered by D. Menzel, 3., 1922-08-01; phaedra2309 (Box 263)
  G18
- [Positions of Nebulae] discovered by D. Menzel, 4., 1922-08-01; phaedra2310 (Box 263)
  G19
- [Positions of Nebulae] Coma-Virgo, 1., 1927-02-01/1927-03-01; phaedra2311 (Box 263)
  G20
  Adelaide Ames
- [Positions of Nebulae] Coma-Virgo, 2., 1927; phaedra2312 (Box 263)
  G21
- [Positions of Nebulae] Coma-Virgo, 3., 1927; phaedra2313 (Box 263)
  G22
- [Positions of Nebulae] Coma-Virgo, 4., phaedra2314 (Box 263)
  G23
- [Positions of Nebulae] Coma-Virgo, 5., phaedra2315 (Box 263)
  G24
- [Diameter, Circumference] Coma-Virgo, 6., phaedra2316 (Box 263)
  G25
- Positions, magnitudes, diameters [Coma-Virgo], 7., phaedra2317 (Box 263)
  G26
- Positions, magnitudes, diameters [Coma-Virgo], 8., phaedra2318 (Box 263)
  G27
- Positions, magnitudes, diameters, S. Gal. Pole, 9., phaedra2319 (Box 263)
  G28
- Positions, magnitudes, diameters Coma-Virgo, -30? to -60?, 10., phaedra2320 (Box 264)
  G29
- Identifications and Magnitudes of NGC Objects, 11., phaedra2321 (Box 264)
  G30
- Identifications and Magnitudes, Coma-Vir. ext., 12., phaedra2322 (Box 264)
  G31
- Plate counts Coma-Vir ext., 13, phaedra2323 (Box 264)
  G32
  Adelaide Ames, R.W. Ford
- Positions of new neb. on A plates, 1., phaedra2324 (Box 264)
  G33
  C.D. Boyd
- Positions of nebulae, 2., phaedra2325 (Box 264)
  G34
  Sylvia F. Mussels
- Positions of nebulae, 3., phaedra2326 (Box 264)
  G35
  Muriel E. Mussels Seyfert
- Positions of nebulae, 4., phaedra2327 (Box 264)
  G36
- Positions of nebulae, 5., phaedra2328 (Box 264)
  G37
- Positions of nebulae, 6., phaedra2329 (Box 264)
  G38
- Positions of nebulae, 7., phaedra2330 (Box 264)
  G39
- Positions of nebulae, 8., phaedra2331 (Box 264)
  G40
- Positions of nebulae, 9., phaedra2332 (Box 264)
  G41
- Positions of nebulae, 10., phaedra2333 (Box 264)
  G42
  Muriel E. Mussels Seyfert, Sylvia F. Mussels
- Positions of nebulae, 11., phaedra2334 (Box 264)
  G43
- Positions of nebulae, 12., phaedra2335 (Box 264)
  G44
- Positions of nebulae, 13., phaedra2336 (Box 264)
  G45
- Positions of nebulae, 14., phaedra2337 (Box 264)
  G46
- Summary of Work Accomplished, A., phaedra2338 (Box 264)
  G47
- Classifications and Diameters, B., phaedra2339 (Box 265)
  G48
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, C., phaedra2340 (Box 265)
  G49
- Classifications and Diameters, D., phaedra2341 (Box 265)
  G50
- Classifications and Diameters, E., phaedra2342 (Box 265)
  G51
- Nebula counter per sq. degree, F., phaedra2343 (Box 265)
  G52
- Magnitudes of clusters of nebulae, G., phaedra2344 (Box 265)
  G53
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, H., phaedra2345 (Box 265)
  G54
- Diameter of brightest nebulae, J., phaedra2346 (Box 265)
  G55
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, K., phaedra2347 (Box 265)
  G56
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, L., phaedra2348 (Box 265)
  G57
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, M., phaedra2349 (Box 265)
  G58
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, N., phaedra2350 (Box 265)
  G59
- Classifications of Nebulae, O., phaedra2351 (Box 265)
  G60
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, P., phaedra2352 (Box 265)
  G61
- Classifications and Diameters of Nebulae, Q., phaedra2353 (Box 265)
  G62
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, R., phaedra2354 (Box 265)
  G63
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, S., phaedra2355 (Box 265)
  G64
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, T., phaedra2356 (Box 265)
  G65
- Classifications of Nebulae, U., phaedra2357 (Box 265)
  G66
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, V., phaedra2358 (Box 265)
  G67
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, W., phaedra2359 (Box 266)
  G68
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, X., phaedra2360 (Box 266)
  G69
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, Y., phaedra2361 (Box 266)
  G70
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, Z., phaedra2362 (Box 266)
  G71
- Examination of A Plates, A'., 1936/1939; phaedra2363 (Box 266)
  G72
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, B'., phaedra2364 (Box 266)
  G73
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, C'., phaedra2365 (Box 266)
  G74
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, D'., phaedra2366 (Box 266)
  G75
  Muriel E. Mussels Seyfert, C.D. Boyd
- Revised Nebula Counts, F'., phaedra2367 (Box 266)
  G76
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, G'., phaedra2368 (Box 266)
  G77
  C.D. Boyd, Francis Woodworth Wright
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, H'., phaedra2369 (Box 266)
  G78
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, I'., phaedra2370 (Box 266)
  G79
- Positions of Nebulae, J'., phaedra2371 (Box 266)
  G80
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, K'., phaedra2372 (Box 266)
  G81
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, L'., phaedra2373 (Box 266)
  G82
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, M'., phaedra2374 (Box 266)
  G83
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, N'., phaedra2375 (Box 266)
  G84
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, O'., phaedra2376 (Box 266)
  G85
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, P'., phaedra2377 (Box 266)
  G86
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, Q'., phaedra2378 (Box 266)
  G87
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, R'., phaedra2379 (Box 266)
  G88
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, S'., phaedra2380 (Box 266)
  G89
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, T'., phaedra2381 (Box 266)
  G90
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, U'., phaedra2382 (Box 266)
  G91
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, V'., phaedra2383 (Box 266)
  G92
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, W'., phaedra2384 (Box 267)
  G93
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, X'., phaedra2385 (Box 267)
  G94
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, Y'., phaedra2386 (Box 267)
  G95
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, Z'., phaedra2387 (Box 267)
  G96
  Francis Woodworth Wright
- Examination of Nebulae, phaedra2388 (Box 267)
  G97
- Coma-Virgo Ext. Magnitudes, vol. 1, 1935; phaedra2389 (Box 267)
  G101
  J. Cuffey
- Coma-Virgo Ext. Magnitudes, vol. 2, 1935; phaedra2390 (Box 267)
  G102
- Nebular Counts, 1935/1937; phaedra2391 (Box 267)
  G103
  B. Lindsay
- Positions of Nebulae, phaedra2392 (Box 267)
  G104
- Magnitudes of Faint Nebulae, phaedra2393 (Box 267)
  G105
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, 1935/1937; phaedra2394 (Box 267)
  G106
- N.G. Cao Magnitudes, phaedra2395 (Box 267)
  G107
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, phaedra2396 (Box 267)
  G108
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, phaedra2397 (Box 267)
  G109
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, phaedra2398 (Box 267)
  G110
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, phaedra2399 (Box 267)
  G111
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, phaedra2400 (Box 267)
  G112
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, phaedra2401 (Box 267)
  G113
- Magnitudes, Diameters of Nebulae, phaedra2402 (Box 267)
  G114
  R.L. Paraboschi
- Magnitudes of Nebulae, phaedra2403 (Box 267)
  G115
- Magnitude on Overlapping Plates, phaedra2404 (Box 267)
  G116
- 15th Magnitude Survey, M1, phaedra2405 (Box 267)
  G117
- 16th Magnitude Survey, M2, phaedra2406 (Box 267)
  G118
- 17th Magnitude Survey, 1935; phaedra2407 (Box 268)
  G119
  N.J. Oliver
- Classifications and Diameters, phaedra2408 (Box 268)
  G125
  C.K. Seyfert
- Classifications and Diameters, phaedra2409 (Box 268)
  G126
- Positions, 1., phaedra2410 (Box 268)
  G127
- Magnitudes, phaedra2411 (Box 268)
  G128
- Magnitudes, phaedra2412 (Box 268)
  G129
- MC Records of Nebulae, summary, phaedra2413 (Box 268)
  G130
- MC Magnitude of Nebulae, phaedra2414 (Box 268)
  G131
- MC Classification and Diameters, phaedra2415 (Box 268)
  G132
- MC Nebulae count, phaedra2416 (Box 268)
  G133
- MC North Polar Cap: Positions, phaedra2417 (Box 268)
  G134
- MC Plate counters, phaedra2418 (Box 268)
  G135
- MC North Polar Cap: Magnitudes, phaedra2419 (Box 268)
  G136
  P.B.J.
- MC North Polar Cap: Magnitudes, phaedra2420 (Box 268)
  G137
- MC Magnitudes, VII, phaedra2421 (Box 268)
  G138
- MC Magnitudes, VIII, phaedra2422 (Box 268)
  G139
- MC Magnitudes, IX, phaedra2423 (Box 268)
  G140
- MC Magnitudes, X, phaedra2424 (Box 268)
  G141
- MC Magnitudes, XI, phaedra2425 (Box 268)
  G142
- MC Magnitudes, XII, phaedra2426 (Box 268)
  G143
- MC Magnitudes, XIII, phaedra2427 (Box 268)
  G144
- MC Magnitudes, XIV, phaedra2428 (Box 268)
  G145
- MC Magnitudes, XV, phaedra2429 (Box 268)
  G146
- Variables in SMC, LMC, 1., 1935/1939; phaedra2430 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail, Francis Woodworth Wright, R.K. Marshall
- Variables in SMC, LMC, 2., phaedra2431 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail, R.A. Craig
- Variables in SMC, LMC, 3., phaedra2432 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail, A.F. Swan
- [Variables] in Vela-Carina, 4., phaedra2433 (Box 269)
- [Variables] in SMC, 5., 1945; phaedra2434 (Box 269)
  A.S. Carlston
- [Variables] in SMC, 6a., phaedra2435 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail, Francis Woodworth Wright
- [Variables] in LMC, SMC, 6b., 1941/1951; phaedra2436 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail, Francis Woodworth Wright, A. Hearn, M.D. Ashbrook
- [Variables] in LMC, SMC, 8., phaedra2437 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail, Virginia McKibben Nail, Francis Woodworth Wright
- [Variables] in SMC, 9., phaedra2438 (Box 269)
  R.K. Marshall, E.M. Cork
- [Variables] in SMC, 10., phaedra2439 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail
- Variables in SMC, 30 Dor (?), 11., phaedra2440 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail, M.R. Hunt
- [Variables] 47 Tuc., 12., phaedra2441 (Box 269)
- [Variables] LMC, SMC, 13., phaedra2442 (Box 269)
  Virginia McKibben Nail, M.S. Matthews
- [Variables], 14., phaedra2443 (Box 269)
- [Variables] SMC, 47 Tuc, NGC362, 15., phaedra2444 (Box 269)
- [Variables] SMC, LMC, 17., phaedra2445 (Box 269)
- [Variables] SMC, 18., 1932; phaedra2446 (Box 269)
  M.B. Leavens
- MWF 182, MWF 188, SMC, LMC, 19., phaedra2447 (Box 269)
  Mildred B. Shapley, Virginia McKibben Nail
- M55, LMC Variable, 28., 1934; phaedra2448 (Box 269)
  Jenka Mohr, Virginia McKibben Nail
- Variables in LMC, 30., 1954/1955; phaedra2449 (Box 269)
- Variables in LMC, 31., 1952; phaedra2450 (Box 269)
  B. Lindsay, Virginia McKibben Nail
- Variables in LMC, 32., phaedra2451 (Box 269)
  M. Ryder
- Variables in LMC, 33., phaedra2452 (Box 269)
- Variables in LMC, SMC, 34., 1950/1954; phaedra2453 (Box 269)
  William G. Tifft, J. Swartzmann
- Variables in LMC (HA 90 #1), 35., phaedra2454 (Box 270)
  Henrietta S. Leavitt, Sylvia F. Mussels
- Variables LMC, 1., phaedra2455 (Box 270)
  Also labeled as FWW1
- Variables SMC, 2., phaedra2456 (Box 270)
  Also labeled as FWW2
- Variables SMC, 3., phaedra2457 (Box 270)
  Also labeled as FWW3
- Red Variables, 4., phaedra2458 (Box 270)
  Also labeled as FWW4
- Variables in NGC1846, 2315, 5., phaedra2459 (Box 270)
  Also labeled as FWW5
- Variables in omega Cen, NGC4833, NGC7099, Var. 1, phaedra2460 (Box 270)
  Also labeled as FWW Var. 1
- Variables in NGC 3201, Var. 2, phaedra2461 (Box 270)
  Also labeled as FWW Var. 2
- Variables in NGC 3201, Var. 3, phaedra2462 (Box 270)
  Also labeled as FWW Var. 3
- Milky Way Bureau, Red Maps, Book 3., phaedra2463 (Box 270)
  Also labeled as FWW Bk.III
- Leo I - periods; Vela, phaedra2464 (Box 270)
  Also labeled as FWW
- Variables in omega Cen, 11., phaedra2465 (Box 270)
  Book in poor condition
- Variables in omega Cen, 12., phaedra2466 (Box 270)
- Variables in omega Cen, 13., phaedra2467 (Box 270)
- Variables in omega Cen.; miscellaneous variables, 17., phaedra2468 (Box 270)
- K. Crucis, phaedra2469 (Box 270)
- Hercules Cluster, phaedra2470 (Box 270)
- Messier 5, 2., phaedra2471 (Box 270)
- Omega Centauri; Eros 2., phaedra2472 (Box 270)
- Measurments of Clusters, no. 1., phaedra2473 (Box 270)
  Book in poor condition.